Bryson Kern

Full Stack Web Developer Tech-savvy Full Stack Web Developer proficient in fundamental frontend languages and server-side languages. Essential knowledge of MySQL and MongoDB. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability, and speed. Creative at heart with a fierce drive to learn.

Contact

Address

Loganville, Georgia, 30052

Phone

(770) 861-9610

E-mail

kernbryson@yahoo.com

Education

2022-02 -	Certificate: Full Stack Web Developer
2022-08	Georgia Institute of Technology - Atlanta
2019-08 - 2022-04	Network Administration
2022 04	Gwinnett Technical College - Lawrenceville, GA
2001-05 - 2019-08	Psychology
	Kennesaw State University - Kennesaw, GA

Programming Languages

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

TypeScript

Projects

Scalpel gitHub: https://github.com/kernbryson/Scalpel-

Personal-Bryson-Kern

Deployed page:

https://scalpelbrysonkern.herokuapp.com/

- Web application that allows users to buy or rent highly sought-after items at the fraction of the price.
- Demonstrated usage of Handlebars JS, express, and sequelize.

VolunteerMe gitHub:

https://github.com/kernbryson/Volunteer-Me Deployed page:

https://volunteermereact.herokuapp.com/

- Application that allows volunteers to find other likeminded volunteers to work with them as well as create volunteer listings.
- Exhibited usage of JWT authentication, React, and GraphQL.

Frameworks

Express

jQuery

Node

React

Handlebars

Databases

MySQL

SQL

MongoDB

GraphQl

Sequelize

Worth The Watch gitHub:

https://github.com/kernbryson/WorthTheWatch Deployed page:

https://kernbryson.github.io/WorthTheWatch/index.html

- Application that helps movie buffs decide what movie to watch and what to expect.
- Illustrated usage of third-party API's, local storage, and BULMA.

PWA Text Editor gitHub:

https://github.com/kernbryson/PWA-Text-Editor-Bryson-V2

Deployed page:

https://pwatexteditor2.herokuapp.com/

- Online text editor that can be downloaded to your machine.
- Displayed usage of webpack's and indexed DB.

Work History

2019-07 - Sales Associate

2022-02

Sherwin Williams Commercial, Alpharetta, GA

- Took on leadership roles by guiding my team at work and directing team outings
- Cross-trained with other store departments and areas, supporting overall retail operations.
- Maintained CRM database, entering new and updated prospect and customer information for use by sales personnel.
- Arranged in-person meetings and visited with clients to improve success of sales pitches.